<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  
  <!-- EN: ocularkin -->
  <VRE_Ocularkin.label>окуляркін</VRE_Ocularkin.label>
  <!-- EN: Based on genetic data retrofitted from Gauranlen Inc.’s investment into dendrology following the Fall of Sorne, phytokins are plant-based humanoids with an emphasis on symmetry and symbiosis. Their ability to subsist only on sunlight and affinity with any and all plantlife make them especially suited to aiding newly established colonies or underperforming industrial farms.\n\nBased on research from the forest planet of Phytok that committed to extensive analysis on human-compatibility with psychic energy, phytokin xenogerms are typically exclusive to high-ranking, supporting roles in megacorporations and planetary governments. Their unique way of reproduction has resulted in many identical offspring, with each generation becoming successively more competent than their progenitor, further contributing to their extremely low numbers. Their affinity with plantlife, along with the side effect of extremely high and ever-increasing psychic sensitivity, mean that any phytokin xenohumans found on the Rim are always adapted to high-concept, dominant trees that are present on their residing planet.\n\nThis particular xenogerm has adapted itself to Ocular trees, a strange breed of alien-looking trees native to a poorly understood extradimensional realm of pure madness. -->
  <VRE_Ocularkin.description>Засновані на генетичних даних, отриманих завдяки інвестиціям Gauranlen Inc. в дендрологію після падіння Сорну, фітокіни - це рослинні гуманоїди з акцентом на симетрію та симбіоз. Їх здатність виживати лише за рахунок сонячного світла та спорідненість з будь-якими рослинами роблять їх особливо придатними для допомоги новоствореним колоніям або недієздатним промисловим фермам.\n\nБазуючись на дослідженнях лісової планети Фіток, які присвячені всебічному аналізу сумісності людини з психічною енергією, ксенозародки фітокінів, як правило, призначені для високопоставлених, допоміжних ролей у мегакорпораціях та планетарних урядах. Їхній унікальний спосіб розмноження призвів до появи великої кількості ідентичних нащадків, причому кожне покоління стає все більш компетентним, ніж їхній предок, що ще більше сприяє їхній вкрай низькій чисельності. Їх спорідненість з рослинним світом, разом з побічним ефектом надзвичайно високої і постійно зростаючої психічної чутливості, означає, що будь-які фітокінні ксенолюди, знайдені на Кільці, завжди пристосовані до домінуючих дерев, присутніх на їхній планеті проживання.\n\nЦей конкретний ксенозародок пристосувався до Окулярних дерев, дивної породи дерев інопланетного вигляду, що походять з погано вивченої позапросторової області чистого божевілля.</VRE_Ocularkin.description>
  <!-- EN: Individualistic and bizarre, ocularkins are warped and cunning and possess an ability to connect with ocular trees. They are excellent at taking care of plants and reproduce via planting a saplingchild. -->
  <VRE_Ocularkin.descriptionShort>Індивідуалістичні та химерні, окуляркіни викривлені та хитрі і мають здатність з'єднуватися з окулярними деревами. Вони чудово доглядають за рослинами і розмножуються, висаджуючи саджанці.</VRE_Ocularkin.descriptionShort>
  
</LanguageData>