<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  
  <!-- EN: malachai -->
  <AG_Malachai.label>малахай</AG_Malachai.label>
  <!-- EN: The Malachai are a race of truly monstrous beings that have evolved from Strigoi. They possess the same thirst for blood as their Strigoi predecessors, but have also learned to incorporate the genetic material of their prey to enhance their own abilities. With their DNA extraction abilities, they can absorb traits such as heightened senses, increased speed, and advanced technological skills, making them an incredibly powerful force.\n\nHowever, their abilities and thirst for power come at a cost, and Malachai are often twisted and cruel in their actions towards others. They harbour a deep-seated hatred for other sanguophages, and will only collaborate with them out of abject necessity. As adept schemers, the Malachai always have an ulterior motive or agenda bubbling beneath the surface of their superficial actions.\n\nTheir society is highly hierarchical and ruthless, with powerful Malachai ruling over weaker ones through fear and intimidation. They are feared by many and considered a dangerous threat to be avoided whenever possible. -->
  <AG_Malachai.description>Малахаї - раса воістину жахливих істот, що походять від Стригоїв. Вони мають таку ж жагу до крові, як і їхні попередники стригої, але також навчилися використовувати генетичний матеріал своєї здобичі для покращення власних здібностей. Завдяки своїм здібностям до екстракції ДНК, вони можуть вбирати в себе такі риси, як загострені почуття, підвищену швидкість і передові технологічні навички, що робить їх неймовірно потужною силою.\n\nОднак, їх здібності і жага до влади мають свою ціну, і Малахаї часто бувають збоченими і жорстокими у своїх діях по відношенню до інших людей. Вони відчувають глибоку ненависть до інших кровопивць і співпрацюють з ними лише через крайню необхідність. Як вправні інтригани, Малахаї завжди мають прихований мотив або план, що кипить під поверхнею їхніх поверхневих дій.\n\nЇхнє суспільство дуже ієрархічне і безжалісне, де сильніші Малахаї керують слабшими за допомогою страху і залякування. Багато хто боїться їх і вважає небезпечною загрозою, якої слід уникати, коли це можливо.</AG_Malachai.description>
  <!-- EN: Malachai are mutated Strigoi: ageless, deathless super-humans powered by archotech-created archites in the bloodstream. They can slowly incorporate genes from their enemies. They can heal any injury, and never suffer from disease or poison. In combat, they use their huge talons to rip their prey to pieces. The price is that they must consume hemogen derived from humans to survive, and they must periodically deathrest for long periods. They lose their hemogen supply and need to replenish it regularly to sustain themselves. They're easily destroyed by fire, and suffer truly extreme penalties in UV light. -->
  <AG_Malachai.descriptionShort>Малахаї - це мутовані Стригої: нестаріючі, безсмертні надлюди, що живляться від створених архонтами архітекторів у крові. Вони можуть повільно інкорпорувати гени своїх ворогів. Вони можуть зцілити будь-яку рану, і ніколи не страждають від хвороб чи отрути. У бою вони використовують свої величезні кігті, щоб розірвати здобич на шматки. Ціна цього полягає в тому, що вони повинні споживати гемоген, отриманий від людей, щоб вижити, і періодично надовго засинати. Вони втрачають свій запас гемогену і повинні регулярно поповнювати його, щоб підтримувати себе. Вони легко знищуються вогнем, а під впливом ультрафіолету зазнають справді екстремальних покарань.</AG_Malachai.descriptionShort>
  
</LanguageData>